http://www.little-brown-cat.com/privacy/

Andover - Cats - Dogs - Horses - Flowers - Birds & Nature - New England Scenery - Potpourri - Holiday Cards
My Special Buddies - Order Info - Privacy - About Us - Contact Us - Home
little brown cat Privacy Policy
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.
little brown cat respects each and every one of our customers' right to Privacy . We do not
sell, trade, or rent any personal information given to little brown cat. We have built our
reputation on service and taking care of our customers beyond their expectations, and we will continue
to provide these levels of service now and for the years to come.
Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to you. We use customer contact information from the registration
form to send the user information about our company and promotional material on new products. Your contact
information is also used to get in touch with you should we have questions regarding your order or should
we need to notify you of the status of your order. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; just contact us and let us know. The financial information we collect is used
only to bill you for products you purchase.
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the site means that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy.
Andover - Cats - Dogs - Horses - Flowers - Birds & Nature - New England Scenery - Potpourri - Holiday Cards
My Special Buddies - Order Info - Privacy - About Us - Contact Us - Home
little brown cat, P.O. Box 4024, Andover, MA 01810 USA Phone: 1-508-523-1611
Copyright © 2004 - 2020 little brown cat
All Rights Reserved
Web Design Cheryl K. Perkins & Associates - Practical Web Development for Small Businesses
